<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<!-- Saellatrix scenes: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="TRANSACTION_START"><![CDATA[
	#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sex_shop_discount))
		<p>
			[saellatrix.speech(As we agreed, you get a 25% discount on everything,)] Saellatrix states in her posh accent.
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sex_shop_penalty))
		<p>
			[saellatrix.speech(As we agreed, you've got to pay double for everything,)] Saellatrix states with an arrogant smirk on her face.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[saellatrix.speech(You've found something you like?)] Saellatrix asks in her posh accent.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<!-- For hard-coded doll brochure dialogue nodes (com/lilithsthrone/game/dialogue/utils/MiscDialogue.java): -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DOLL_BROCHURE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to see the prices and options for purchasing a doll, you ask Saellatrix if you can take a look at the sales brochure.
	</p>
	<p>
		Placing the black-and-gold booklet down on the counter before you, the succubus opens it
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sex_shop_discount))
			 and asks in a slightly annoyed voice, [saellatrix.speech(Wanting to take advantage of your discount? Fine, we'll still be making a nice profit on anything you order...)]
		#ELSEIF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sex_shop_penalty))
			 and says with a wicked smirk on her face, [saellatrix.speech(Don't forget how you lost our wager; I've had all of the prices in this particular brochure doubled. You'll be paying extra until you finally submit to me...)]
		#ELSE
			 and says in a polite voice, [saellatrix.speech(Please take your time.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DOLL_BROCHURE_RACE_SELECTION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After you've told Saellatrix what options you'd like for your doll order, she asks in an approving tone, [saellatrix.speech(You'd like a special edition anthro doll? What an excellent choice. What race would you like it to be?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Producing a list of available races from under the counter, the succubus places it down before you and states, [saellatrix.speech(For obvious reasons, slimes aren't available. We also don't have any angel, demon, or dragon dolls. Several other races are incompatible with the nature of our dolls' silicone bodies, so what you see on the list is everything we're able to provide. Hopefully we'll be able to offer a wider selection of races at some point in the future.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking down at the list of races which are available, you make your choice...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DOLL_BROCHURE_FINISHED_STANDARD"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After you've told Saellatrix what options you'd like for your doll order, she says in a rather insincere tone, [saellatrix.speech(Excellent choices. Now let me just write this down...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DOLL_BROCHURE_FINISHED_SPECIAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After you've told Saellatrix what race you'd like your doll to be, she says in a rather insincere tone, [saellatrix.speech(Very well. Now let me just write this down...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DOLL_BROCHURE_FINISHED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]==0)
			[saellatrix.speech(You want a standard DD model,)]
		#ELSEIF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]==1)
			[saellatrix.speech(You want a premium HH model,)]
		#ELSE
			[saellatrix.speech(You want a special edition [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1] model,)]
		#ENDIF
		 the succubus says while writing down your preferences,
		#IF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_2]==0)
			[saellatrix.speech(with the default pussy-only option,
		#ELSEIF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_2]==1)
			[saellatrix.speech(with the option of having no pussy and a cock,
		#ELSE
			[saellatrix.speech(with the option of having both a pussy and a cock,
		#ENDIF
		 and
		#IF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_3]==0)
			 with the default body of an eighteen year old.
		#ELSEIF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_3]==1)
			 with an aged body of a twenty-five year old.
		#ELSEIF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_3]==2)
			 with an aged body of a thirty-five year old.
		#ELSEIF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_3]==3)
			 with an aged body of a forty-five year old.
		#ELSEIF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_3]==4)
			 with an aged body of a fifty-five year old.
		#ELSEIF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_3]==5)
			 with an aged body of a sixty-five year old.
		#ENDIF
		)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Pausing briefly to push her thick-rimmed glasses up her nose, Saellatrix then quickly jots down your other choices while speaking out loud, [saellatrix.speech(
		#IF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_4]==0)
			No clothing is to be provided,
		#ELSEIF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_4]==1)
			Your doll will be delivered in rainbow gloves and stockings,
		#ELSEIF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_4]==2)
			Your doll will be delivered in cat-style lingerie,
		#ELSE
			Your doll will be delivered in a maid uniform,
		#ENDIF
		#IF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_5])
			 and she'll come equipped with a selection of toys.
		#ELSE
			 and you don't want the toy set.
		#ENDIF
		#IF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_6])
			 We'll have the barcode on her head removed before delivery,
		#ELSE
			 The barcode on her head isn't to be removed,
		#ENDIF
		#IF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_7])
			 and we'll plug her into a D.E.C.K. and give her a head of hair.
		#ELSE
			 and we're not to use a D.E.C.K. to give her any hair.
		#ENDIF
		 Is that all correct so far?
		)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Confirming that that's what you want, you listen as Saellatrix makes the final notes, continuing to speak out loud as she does so, [saellatrix.speech(
		#IF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_8])
			Speaking of a D.E.C.K., you want to purchase one with your doll order.
		#ELSE
			Speaking of a D.E.C.K., you don't want to purchase one with your doll order.
		#ENDIF
		#IF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_9])
			 You've also chosen my favourite option; you want me to fuck your doll before delivery. I do always enjoy growing a nice, big cock and pounding a doll's holes before shipping them off.
		#ELSE
			 You've also decided not to go for my favourite option; you don't want your doll fucked before delivery.
		#ENDIF
		 Ok, so that'll be [#SPECIAL_PARSE_10] flames, please.
		#IF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_8])
			 I'll fetch you a D.E.C.K. as soon as I've received payment.
		#ENDIF
		)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the succubus looks expectantly at you, waiting for you to produce the flames...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DOLL_BROCHURE_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Producing the flames which Saellatrix is asking for, you hand them over to the succubus, who says in a slightly condescending manner, [saellatrix.speech(I'm sure that you'll enjoy your purchase. We'll have your doll brought out and kept in the storage area over there.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After pointing over to the other side of the shop to show you where she means, Saellatrix then says, [saellatrix.speech(We'll hold onto your doll until you're ready to take delivery of it. Thank you for your purchase.)]
	</p>
	#IF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_0])
		<p>
			Bending down to unlock a cabinet beneath her counter, Saellatrix produces the D.E.C.K. you've ordered and sets it down on the surface before you. Looking down at it, you see that it's one of this world's very rare examples of a computer-like device, complete with a durable-looking touchscreen and a thick cable which ends in a three-pronged plug. As you take possession of this device, Saellatrix smugly states, [saellatrix.speech(That's the very latest in cutting-edge technology. Plug it in to a doll's port on the rear of their neck, and you can use the screen to transform them.)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		Pushing her thick-rimmed glasses up her nose once more, the succubus asks, [saellatrix.speech(Will that be all, or would you like to purchase anything else?)]
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'><i>
		To take delivery of your doll, you need to install a doll closet in Lilaya's mansion, then once located in that closet's tile, you can move your doll there via the management screen.
	</i></p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	
	<!-- Main shop scenes: -->
	
	<!-- Entrance: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENTER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking hold of its golden handle, you push open the glass door and [pc.step] into Loveienne's Luxuries. To your left and right, you see numerous sleek, glass shelving units, each one of which is stocked full of all sorts of sex toys and fetish gear. To your far right, past the shelving units, you see that dozens of black, silicone sex dolls have been lined up against the wall. Directly ahead, linked to the door behind you by a red strip of carpet, is the shop's counter, behind which is standing
		#IF(saellatrix.isPlayerKnowsName())
			 Saellatrix.
		#ELSE
			 a big-chested succubus wearing a smart black blazer.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		There are several dozen shoppers within the store, and from their smart outfits and the way they hold themselves, they all give off the impression of being very wealthy. To either side of the entrance, and scattered throughout the store, are tall, muscular wolf-boy security guards. With such a heavy security presence, you're convinced that this store's clientèle must be very important and wealthy indeed.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="EXIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Finding yourself standing at the entrance to Lovienne's Luxuries, you turn to face the store and take a look around. To your left and right, you see numerous sleek, glass shelving units, each one of which is stocked full of all sorts of sex toys and fetish gear. To your far right, past the shelving units, you see that dozens of black, silicone sex dolls have been lined up against the wall. Directly ahead, linked to the door behind you by a red strip of carpet, is the shop's counter, behind which is standing
		#IF(saellatrix.isPlayerKnowsName())
			 Saellatrix.
		#ELSE
			 a big-chested succubus wearing a smart black blazer.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		There are several dozen shoppers within the store, and from their smart outfits and the way they hold themselves, they all give off the impression of being very wealthy. To either side of the entrance, and scattered throughout the store, are tall, muscular wolf-boy security guards. With such a heavy security presence, you're convinced that this store's clientèle must be very important and wealthy indeed.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EXIT_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had enough of Lovienne's Luxuries, you push open the glass door and head back out into the streets of Demon Home...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="FLOOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The main floor of the store is filled with glass shelving units, upon which countless types of sex toys are on display. You pass by dildos, vibrators, and butt-plugs of all shapes, sizes, and colours, before entering an aisle which specialises in latex fetish gear. After that, there's another section dedicated to sex toys, and then you're passing by collars, restraints, and other such BDSM accessories.
	</p>
	<p>
		If there's anything which takes your fancy, it'd be best to head on over to the counter to complete your purchase...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<!-- Display & demo doll: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DISPLAY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		In one corner of the store, a square section of marble flooring has been cordoned off with red rope barriers. Within this space are located three black silicone sex dolls, each one of which is completely identical to the others. The first doll is lying on her back with her legs spread, while the second is sitting on the first one's face. The third is performing a standing split beside the second, with her exposed groin hovering right next to the second's face.
	</p>
	<p>
		Although their pussies, assholes, and mouths have been left empty, you can quite clearly see that bright-pink dildos have been shoved deep into these dolls' fuckable nipples.
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sex_shop_display_on))
			 These dildos are noisily buzzing away as they vibrate with a powerful intensity, causing the dolls' DD-cup breasts to jiggle and jump about in the process. Clearly having been ordered to act only while the toys are turned on, the once-motionless dolls are rubbing their clits and letting out horny moans, with the first greedily eating out the second and the second 
			#IF(game.isAnalContentEnabled())
				 hungrily rimming the third.
			#ELSE
				 doing the same to the third.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 Despite the fact that they're holding awkward poses and have their breasts stuffed full of sex toys, the dolls are all completely and utterly motionless.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		A smart-looking pedestal is positioned beside this display area, with a large pink button on top being labelled as controlling the dildos' vibration, which in turn will animate the dolls or make them remain motionless.
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sex_shop_display_on))
			 If you wanted to, you could press this button and turn off the dildos, bringing the dolls to a halt.
		#ELSE
			 If you wanted to, you could press this button and turn on the dildos, bringing the dolls to life.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		As well as these three dolls, you see that a fourth is squatting on the floor in front of the display. Unlike all of the others, who are coloured black, this doll is bright pink, and has a glossy, shiny finish to her which makes her appear to be made out of latex. Beneath the white barcode that's tattooed onto her forehead, the words 'DEMONSTRATION MODEL - NOT FOR SALE' have been inked into her skin.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="DISPLAY_TRIO_BUTTON"><![CDATA[
	#IF(!flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sex_shop_display_on))
		<p>
			Deciding to give the dolls a break, you press the button, turning their sex toys off. Immediately, the bright pink dildos inserted into their fuckable nipples stop vibrating, and with that the three dolls stop moving. Remaining completely and utterly motionless, the sex dolls could easily be mistaken for statues.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Deciding to give the dolls some fun, you press the button, turning their sex toys on. Immediately, the bright pink dildos inserted into their fuckable nipples start vibrating, and with that all three of them reach down and start rhythmically rubbing their clits. Letting out lewd moans, they start to perform oral on one another, with the first greedily eating out the second and the second 
			#IF(game.isAnalContentEnabled())
				 hungrily rimming the third.
			#ELSE
				 doing the same to the third.
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DISPLAY_DEMO_DOLL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Finding yourself drawn to the shiny pink doll, you [pc.step] over to where she's squatting down on the floor. From here, you're able to see that she's rhythmically rubbing her clit as she slowly lifts herself up and down, forcing a massive, ribbed dildo in and out of her cunt. Thanks to the mirrored section of floor upon which she's squatting, you're able to see her cunt stretching lewdly around the huge toy, as well as the end of a jewelled-heart buttplug that's been securely pushed into her asshole. With her free hand, she's cupping and groping her [demoDoll.cupSize]-cup breasts, and occasionally sliding her fingers into her fuckable nipples.
	</p>
	<p>
		A sign next to this pink doll names her as the shop's 'demo doll', and instructs customers to use her to find out how good Lovienne's sex dolls are at performing oral. Permission is given to cum in and on the doll as much as you want, but any sex action other than oral is strictly forbidden, with the doll having been instructed to call security if you try anything else with her.
	</p>
	<p>
		Continuing to masturbate, the doll looks up at you and asks in a feminine, yet slightly robotic voice, [demoDoll.speech(Would you like to use my mouth, [pc.master]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DISPLAY_DEMO_DOLL_BLOWJOB_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the sound of getting a blowjob from this demo doll, you pull out your [pc.cock+] and present it to her. Obediently opening her mouth wide, she lets out a horny moan and begs, [demoDoll.speech(Please, [pc.master], fuck my throat! Be as rough as you like...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		At the sight of this naked, slutty doll telling you to use her, your cock quickly rises to attention, and you waste no time in pushing the [pc.cockHead+] into her mouth. Hungrily wrapping her [demoDoll.lips+] around your hard shaft, the doll slides her head forwards and swallows your cock as she beings to give you a blowjob...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DISPLAY_DEMO_DOLL_CUNNILINGUS_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the sound of receiving cunnilingus from this demo doll, you expose your [pc.pussy+] and present it to her. Obediently opening her mouth wide and sticking out her tongue, she lets out a horny moan and begs, [demoDoll.speech(Please, [pc.master], let me taste your cunt...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		At the sight of this naked, slutty doll begging for your pussy, you feel yourself getting turned on, and you waste no time in pushing your [pc.labia+] down against her mouth. Hungrily pressing her [demoDoll.lips+] to your pussy, the doll slides her tongue into your twat and starts to eat you out...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DISPLAY_DEMO_DOLL_BACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you're not interested in using the demo doll right now, you [pc.step] away from her...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DISPLAY_DEMO_DOLL_BLOWJOB_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had your fun with the demo doll, you get her to give your cock a few last licks, before [pc.stepping] back and bringing an end to the sex.
	</p>
	<p>
		[demoDoll.speech(I hope that I was to your satisfaction, [pc.master],)] she says as you get your things back in order. Reaching over to grab a wet wipe from behind the nearby sign, the demo doll quickly cleans herself up, before starting to once again rhythmically rub her clit and bounce up and down on the massive dildo.
	</p>
	#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sex_shop_oral_offer))
		<p>
			Leaving the shiny pink doll behind, you start to [pc.walk] away from the display area, wondering what to do next...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[saellatrix.speech(I couldn't help but watch that little performance,)] the posh voice of Saellatrix sounds out from behind you. Turning to face the succubus, you watch as she steps forwards and reveals a sadistic streak by unexpectedly delivering a vicious, sharp slap to the demo doll's face. The pink doll appears to be totally unaffected by this abuse, for she continues masturbating as though nothing happened while the succubus addresses you, [saellatrix.speech(That big cock of yours is wasted on this hole. How about the two of us have a little wager?)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DISPLAY_DEMO_DOLL_BLOWJOB_END_OFFER_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wondering what this is all about, you ask Saellatrix what it is she has in mind.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(You let me suck that delicious-looking dick of yours, and if you manage to snap my choker in the process, I'll give you a lifetime 25% discount,)] she offers while playfully tugging at the black, velvet choker that's tightly hugging her neck. Allowing a sinister expression to settle on her face, she takes a step towards you, and while using her spaded tail to playfully stroke your crotch, she evilly sneers, [saellatrix.speech(If you fail to snap it, you'll have to pay double for everything instead. That is, unless you let me fuck you raw. In case I'm not being clear, that means I'll grow a nice, fat cock and shove every last inch of it inside of you.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can respond, the succubus places her index finger over your [pc.lips], before saying, [saellatrix.speech(No need to rush. Let me know when you're ready for it.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the succubus strides back to her counter, her [saellatrix.ass+] swaying in a hypnotic manner as she goes. Left standing beside the display area, you wonder what to do now...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DISPLAY_DEMO_DOLL_CUNNILINGUS_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had your fun with the demo doll, you get her to give your pussy a few last licks, before [pc.stepping] back and bringing an end to the sex.
	</p>
	<p>
		[demoDoll.speech(I hope that I was to your satisfaction, [pc.master],)] she says as you get your things back in order. Reaching over to grab a wet wipe from behind the nearby sign, the demo doll quickly cleans herself up, before starting to once again rhythmically rub her clit and bounce up and down on the massive dildo.
	</p>
	<p>
		Leaving the shiny pink doll behind, you start to [pc.walk] away from the display area, wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<!-- Dolls: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DOLLS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Along the right-hand wall of the shop, several dozen sex dolls have been lined up in regimented ranks. Each one of them is completely identical, being made out of black silicone and taking the appearance of a human female in her early twenties. Thanks to the fact that they're not wearing a single item of clothing, and that they're completely bald, you're able to see that each one of them has a white barcode tattooed onto their forehead.
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking a closer look at their bodies, you can't help but be impressed by the absurd level of detail each one of these dolls possesses. Every single feature of a real body has been replicated in black silicone, right down to the cuticles of each nail, the correct number and shape of individual eyelashes, and even the pores on their faux skin. In fact, it would almost be believable if someone told you that they were real people, just made out of silicone instead of flesh.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER"><![CDATA[
	#IF(!saellatrix.isPlayerKnowsName())
		<p>
			Crossing the shop floor, you approach the counter, behind which is standing a smartly-dressed succubus. The first thing which you can't help but notice is the fact that she has a massive pair of [saellatrix.cupSize]-cup breasts, which are threatening to burst out of her smart black blazer at any moment. Looking past her sizeable assets, you see a pair of thick-rimmed glasses sitting on the beautiful face of a woman in her late thirties. Her dark red skin fades into black at the tips of her long, upright horns, and black again is the colour of her shoulder-length, bob-cut hair.
		</p>
		<p>
			As you approach, you're able to see down over the top of the counter, allowing you to notice that the succubus is wearing a very short miniskirt, while a pair of black stockings are covering her long, smooth legs. Looking back up to her face, you see that a pair of yellow, snake-like eyes are closely following your every move. Finally, as you come to a halt before her, you see that she's wearing a black velvet choker around her neck.
		</p>
		<p>
			[saellatrix.speech(I don't believe that I've had the pleasure,)] the succubus says in a silky-smooth, posh British accent. Giving you a polite smile which has very little sincerity to it, she waits for you to introduce yourself...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Crossing the shop floor, you approach the counter, behind which the familiar, smartly-dressed form of Saellatrix is standing. The first thing which you can't help but notice is the fact that she has a massive pair of [saellatrix.cupSize]-cup breasts, which are threatening to burst out of her smart black blazer at any moment. Looking past her sizeable assets, you see a pair of thick-rimmed glasses sitting on the beautiful face of a woman in her late thirties. Her dark red skin fades into black at the tips of her long, upright horns, and black again is the colour of her shoulder-length, bob-cut hair.
		</p>
		<p>
			As you approach, you're able to see down over the top of the counter, allowing you to notice that the succubus is wearing a very short miniskirt, while a pair of black stockings are covering her long, smooth legs. Looking back up to her face, you see that a pair of yellow, snake-like eyes are closely following your every move. Finally, as you come to a halt before her, you see that she's wearing a black velvet choker around her neck.
		</p>
		#IF(saellatrix.isVisiblyPregnant())
			#IF(!saellatrix.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(pc))
				<p>
					Pointedly rubbing her hands over her swollen, [style.colourSex(pregnant belly)], the succubus calmly states in her posh British accent, [saellatrix.speech(Yes, you got me pregnant. No, this doesn't grant you any special privileges. If you think that knocking me up makes us an item, you're very much mistaken.)]
				</p>
			#ELSE
				<p>
					Pointedly rubbing her hands over her swollen, [style.colourSex(pregnant belly)], the succubus calmly states in her posh British accent, [saellatrix.speech(Yes, I'm still pregnant, thanks to you. No, still don't get any special privileges. If you think that knocking me up makes us an item, you're very much mistaken.)]
				</p>
			#ENDIF
			<p>
				As she's the mother of your children, you feel like you should at least try to talk to Saellatrix about it. Before you can get out a single word, however, the succubus anticipates what it is you're going to say and interrupts you.
			</p>
			#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sex_shop_discount))
				<p>
					[saellatrix.speech(Don't even try to offer me any help. I don't need it, I don't want it,)] Saellatrix firmly states. With the matter of her pregnancy seemingly dealt with, the succubus suddenly opens her mouth, allowing her abnormally-long tongue to loll out in order to give you an unobstructed view of her tentacle-lined throat. After playfully licking her [saellatrix.lips+], she closes her mouth and offers in a seductive tone,
					#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sex_shop_saellatrix_sex))
						 [saellatrix.speech(I don't have any more time today, but if you'd like to repeat my wager tomorrow, you know where to find me...)]
					#ELSE
						 [saellatrix.speech(You've already earned your discount, but if you'd like to repeat my wager, I'm always game. Snap my choker and keep your discount, fail to snap it and you have to pay double for everything. Interested?)]
					#ENDIF
				</p>
			#ELSEIF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sex_shop_penalty))
				<p>
					[saellatrix.speech(Don't even try to offer me any help. I don't need it, I don't want it,)] Saellatrix firmly states. With the matter of her pregnancy seemingly dealt with, the succubus allows an arrogant smirk to settle on her beautiful face as she offers,
					#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sex_shop_saellatrix_sex))
						 [saellatrix.speech(I don't have any more time today, but if you'd like me to stop charging you double for everything, all you'll have to do is submit. I know you'll do it, so come back to me tomorrow...)]
					#ELSE
						 [saellatrix.speech(If you'd like me to stop charging you double for everything, all you have to do is submit. Let me rail you with my fat cock and I'll let you buy my goods at normal prices.)]
					#ENDIF
				</p>
			#ELSEIF(saellatrix.getTotalTimesHadSex(pc)>0)
				<p>
					[saellatrix.speech(Don't even try to offer me any help. I don't need it, I don't want it,)] Saellatrix firmly states. With the matter of her pregnancy seemingly dealt with, the succubus suddenly opens her mouth, allowing her abnormally-long tongue to loll out in order to give you an unobstructed view of her tentacle-lined throat. After playfully licking her [saellatrix.lips+], she closes her mouth and offers in a seductive tone,
					#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sex_shop_saellatrix_sex))
						 [saellatrix.speech(I don't have any more time today, but if you'd like to repeat my wager tomorrow, you know where to find me...)]
					#ELSE
						 [saellatrix.speech(If you'd like to repeat my wager, I'm always game. Snap my choker and earn a 25% discount, fail to snap it and you have to pay double for everything. Interested?)]
					#ENDIF
				</p>
			#ELSE
				<p>
					[saellatrix.speech(Don't even try to offer me any help. I don't need it, I don't want it,)] Saellatrix firmly states. With the matter of her pregnancy seemingly dealt with, the succubus gives you another of her polite, insincere smiles as she waits to hear what it is you want of her...
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sex_shop_discount))
				<p>
					[saellatrix.speech([pc.Name], I was just thinking about you,)] Saellatrix teases in her silky-smooth, posh British accent. Opening her mouth, she allows her abnormally-long tongue to loll out, giving you an unobstructed view of her tentacle-lined throat. After playfully licking her [saellatrix.lips+], she closes her mouth and offers in a seductive tone,
					#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sex_shop_saellatrix_sex))
						 [saellatrix.speech(I don't have any more time today, but if you'd like to repeat my wager tomorrow, you know where to find me...)]
					#ELSE
						 [saellatrix.speech(You've already earned your discount, but if you'd like to repeat my wager, I'm always game. Snap my choker and keep your discount, fail to snap it and you have to pay double for everything. Interested?)]
					#ENDIF
				</p>
			#ELSEIF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sex_shop_penalty))
				<p>
					[saellatrix.speech([pc.Name], I was just thinking about how much money I'm going to make from you,)] Saellatrix teases in her silky-smooth, posh British accent. Allowing an arrogant smirk to settle on her beautiful face, she offers,
					#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sex_shop_saellatrix_sex))
						 [saellatrix.speech(I don't have any more time today, but if you'd like me to stop charging you double for everything, all you'll have to do is submit. I know you'll do it, so come back to me tomorrow...)]
					#ELSE
						 [saellatrix.speech(If you'd like me to stop charging you double for everything, all you have to do is submit. Let me rail you with my fat cock and I'll let you buy my goods at normal prices.)]
					#ENDIF
				</p>
			#ELSEIF(saellatrix.getTotalTimesHadSex(pc)>0)
				<p>
					[saellatrix.speech([pc.Name], I was just thinking about you,)] Saellatrix teases in her silky-smooth, posh British accent. Opening her mouth, she allows her abnormally-long tongue to loll out, giving you an unobstructed view of her tentacle-lined throat. After playfully licking her [saellatrix.lips+], she closes her mouth and offers in a seductive tone,
					#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sex_shop_saellatrix_sex))
						 [saellatrix.speech(I don't have any more time today, but if you'd like to repeat my wager tomorrow, you know where to find me...)]
					#ELSE
						 [saellatrix.speech(If you'd like to repeat my wager, I'm always game. Snap my choker and earn a 25% discount, fail to snap it and you have to pay double for everything. Interested?)]
					#ENDIF
				</p>
			#ELSE
				<p>
					[saellatrix.speech([pc.Name], how wonderful it is to see you again,)] Saellatrix greets you in her silky-smooth, posh British accent. Giving you another of her polite, insincere smiles, she waits to hear what it is you want of her...
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_STEP_BACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Telling Saellatrix that you want to take another look at the goods on sale in her shop, you [pc.step] away from the counter.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(Please let me know if you require any assistance,)] the succubus says, [saellatrix.speech(Oh, and please do use the demonstration doll as much as you'd like.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Moving away from the counter, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_INTRO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Giving the succubus your name, you ask her if she's the owner of this store.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(That's correct,)] she replies. Her accent and the way she looks slightly down her nose at you as she speaks gives her a haughty, somewhat-arrogant mannerism. Clearly relishing this opportunity to show off, she pauses for a moment and allows a smirk to settle on her beautiful face, before revealing, [saellatrix.speech(I am <i>the</i> Saellatrix Loviennemartuilani; recognised daughter of the elder lilin Lovienne, I own and manage this store in my mother's name. This is the only place in the entire realm where you can purchase one of my mother's premium sex dolls. No other doll comes close to their realism, autonomy, or durability. Not to mention how good they feel to <i>fuck</i>.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		This last word is said with some emphasis, and for a moment a very sincere, yet oddly sinister smile flashes across the succubus's face. Before you can think too much of it, Saellatrix continues in her posh accent, [saellatrix.speech(Of course, our dolls command a high price, as is befitting of anything created by an elder lilin. Please inform me if you'd like to know more about our dolls. Or, if you're simply here for a sex toy, then we have a wide range for sale.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Saellatrix stops talking, and after pushing her glasses up onto the bridge of her nose, she gives you another of her insincere smiles and waits to hear what it is you want...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_TALK_BACKGROUND"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Curious to hear how Saellatrix, as a recognised daughter of an elder lilin, ended up being the manager of a sex toy shop, you ask her what led to her being here.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(Oh, do you think it's beneath my station to be working?)] she asks in an arrogant tone. Not waiting for an answer, she continues, [saellatrix.speech(Ordinarily, that would be the case. A recognised daughter, lowering herself by choosing to work for a living? How wretched. This, however, is not an ordinary shop.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Wanting her to reveal more details of her past, you ask Saellatrix what makes this particular store so special.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(Why, because it bears the name of an elder lilin, of course,)] the succubus replies, [saellatrix.speech(I technically own the premises, but I purchased this establishment and set up this business on behalf of my mother. Thanks to the exceptional sex dolls which she creates, this is one of the most profitable ventures in all Dominion. My customers should feel privileged to know that their money is directly supporting the luxurious life of their betters; that being, myself and Lovienne.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Pushing her to find out more about her background, you ask the succubus what she did before setting up this shop.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(The usual,)] she replies with a wave of her hand, [saellatrix.speech(Playing politics and crushing my siblings until I caught my mother's eye. From there it was a simple matter to get recognised, really. When I showed up to a ball with two dozen of my sisters willingly crawling behind me in chains, mother knew that I was worthy of her. After I was recognised, she told me that she'd perfected a method of creating sex dolls, and just needed somewhere to sell them. Hence, here I am. Satisfied now?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		From the tone in Saellatrix's voice, you can tell that her patience is starting to wear thin. Thinking that it's best not to ask any more questions on this subject, you wonder what to say next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_TALK_LOVIENNE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to hear more about Saellatrix's mother, you ask her what she can tell you about the elder lilin Lovienne.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(You don't know about mother?)] Saellatrix incredulously asks with one eyebrow raised. [saellatrix.speech(It's every citizen's duty to learn about their rulers. You at least know that Lovienne, along with her sister Lasielle, has the highest honour of guarding Lilith herself?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Thinking that it's best to answer in the affirmative, you tell the succubus that you did know that.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(Oh, I see, so you already do know about Lovienne. You just wanted to hear some juicy gossip from a recognised daughter of hers, is that it?)] she asks. Tutting at you before you can answer, Saellatrix goes on, [saellatrix.speech(Well, I suppose I could always confirm a couple of rumours which seem to have spread through the whole of Dominion. Yes, Lasielle does absolutely anything which mother asks of her, and no, the fact that they're sisters doesn't stop them from fucking each other senseless.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		A slight smirk flashes across Saellatrix's face as she finishes saying that, before revealing one last detail, [saellatrix.speech(Oh, and that other rumour is quite true as well; mother is Lilith's favourite, and often spends the night in her chambers. As to what they do in there together, well, I'm sure you can use your imagination.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Crossing her arms beneath her massive breasts, Saellatrix looks down her nose at you and stops talking, making it clear that she doesn't want to talk with you about her mother any more...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Doll quest: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_ANGELIXX_DIARY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Even after having had the factory tour, you've got no clue as to where the kidnapped refugees might be. Running out of options, you decide to confront Saellatrix with the contents of Angelixx's diary, and after producing the little pink book, you tell the succubus that her sister has written about teleporting illegally enslaved refugees here.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(Angelixx has always had a fanciful imagination, so I wouldn't believe anything that she's written in her diary if I were you,)] the succubus calmly responds. Her normal, posh accent doesn't betray any hint of emotion as she tries to gain the initiative by asking, [saellatrix.speech(How did you obtain my sister's diary? I doubt that she would have simply given it away, and the last time I checked, theft was a serious crime.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not wanting to be accused of a crime by such a powerful, high-ranking demon, you defend yourself by telling Saellatrix that Angelixx had abandoned it. Hoping to try and get some information on where her sister might be hiding, you tell the succubus that you'll give it back to Angelixx if you can meet her.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(Don't try to make demands of me,)] Saellatrix icily responds. Taking you by surprise, she displays her proficiency with the arcane, and with a simple telekinetic spell, she pulls the diary from out of your grip. A triumphant sneer settles on her face as she securely locks the diary away in a drawer beneath the counter, before shouting, [saellatrix.speech(Security!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can react, a pair of burly wolf-boys have flanked you and grabbed you by the [pc.arms]. Shaking her head, Saellatrix sighs, [saellatrix.speech(I'll hear no more nonsense about the fantasies my sister writes in her silly little diary. My boys here will show you out, and when you return, the two of us will pretend that this little incident never happened.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not giving you a chance to respond, the succubus nods to her security guards, and they begin to firmly lead you over to the exit...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_ANGELIXX_DIARY_THROWN_OUT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Leading you across the shop floor in a matter of seconds, the two wolf-boys open the door and give you a forceful shove to encourage you to leave. Not wanting to make a scene, and with nothing to gain by protesting against this treatment, you [pc.step] out into Demon Home and hear the door swing shut behind you.
	</p>
	#IF(game.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_MAGIC_STORM)
		<p>
			As a lightning flash illuminates your surroundings in a pinkish hue, you look across the street to see a familiar person waving at you from within a packed bar. The person in question is Fiammetta, the reporter who you briefly met in Lovienne's Luxuries while Saellatrix was showing you her dolls. Clearly being unable to leave the bar due to the ongoing storm, the short, black-haired woman remains where she is while energetically motioning for you to come over to her.
		</p>
		<p>
			Deciding that you've got nothing to lose by listening to what it is she has to say, you cross the street and enter the bar. No sooner has the sound-proof door swung shut behind you, Fiammetta has bounded over to you and excitedly asks, [fiammetta.speech(You got banned from her shop as well?! I saw you get thrown out!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			As you [pc.step] out into the street, you suddenly see a familiar person skipping directly towards you. The person in question is Fiammetta, the reporter who you briefly met in Lovienne's Luxuries while Saellatrix was showing you her dolls. Skidding to a halt right in front of you, the short, black-haired woman excitedly asks, [fiammetta.speech(You got banned from her shop as well?! I saw you get thrown out!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		Telling her that you're not banned, just momentarily not welcome, you ask Fiammetta why she's so excited about it.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fiammetta.speech(Heh, well if you're on Sae's bad side, I figured that you might want to get back at her by helping me out with something,)] she reveals. Letting out a little sigh, she crosses her arms under her small, B-cup breasts  and says, [fia.speech(Apart from insults, there are only a few things you can say to Sae to get her to kick you out like that, and I doubt you were standing there calling her a bitch. You asked her about how her dolls are <i>really</i> made, or if she has anything to do with the disappearances that started here in Dominion and then moved to Elis. Am I right?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Seeing an opportunity to find out more about the kidnapped refugees, you briefly tell Fiammetta about Angelixx's involvement, and what you read in her diary.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(I knew she was the one behind it!)] the reporter exclaims, before telling you her side of the story, [fia.speech(I started investigating a series of disappearances here in Dominion over a year ago, but just as I began to hear the name 'Angelixx', the gang she was supposedly leading suddenly vanished, and the disappearances stopped. The next thing I heard, it was now refugees over in Elis who were going missing. Some hushed words in a seedy pub from a former member of Angelixx's gang suggested that those who vanished were being taken to Sae's shop, but there was no real proof. What you've just told me confirms that it's real. Angelixx is providing her sister with a supply of illegal slaves.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		From what was written in Agelixx's diary, that does look to be the case. Recalling what Fiammetta said when you first met her, you ask her if there might be any truth behind the rumour of dolls being made from real people.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(Oh, no, I'm certain that Sae's only motive is to make a killing on running what must be one of Dominion's largest illegal slave trade networks. Besides, I was the one to start that rumour about dolls being people!)] she laughs, [fia.speech(I was at a dead end in my investigation and thought that kicking the hornet's nest might get the Enforcers involved, and then they might discover Sae's illegal slave trade. That didn't happen. All that my rumour achieved was Sae throwing together an obviously fake factory and then offering tours of it to placate the public. I guess she didn't want any potential rivals seeing her real factory and then copying her method of making dolls.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Having heard enough of all this for now, you ask Fiammetta what it is that she wanted your help with.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fiammetta.speech(I'm going to find where Sae's keeping those kidnapped people!)] she confidently replies, before imagining the headlines out-loud, [fiammetta.speech('Saellatrix Selling Illegal Slaves', or 'Recognised Daughter of Lovienne Responsible for Kidnappings'. It'd be the scandal of the decade, and I'd be the one to break the story! But I can't do it alone; I need a partner in crime. Interested?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_ANGELIXX_DIARY_THROWN_OUT_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wondering what Fiammetta's plan is, you ask her what it is she's got in mind.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(I knew you'd be up for it!)] she exclaims in premature excitement. Leaning in close, she conspiratorially whispers, [fia.speech(We're going to break into Sae's shop in the dead of night, sneak into whatever offices she has, and find evidence of where she's keeping all those illegal slaves.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Although you do want to find out what Angelixx and Saellatrix have done with all the kidnapped people from Dominion and Elis, the fact that you'll be committing a crime against one of the most important people in all the Realm causes you to hesitate. As Saellatrix has the same social standing as Lilaya, your demonic aunt might not be able to get you out of this if you're caught in the act.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(Don't worry, I've already cased the joint, and all but one of the security guards are off duty between one and four in the morning. So as long as we can sneak past just one guard then there's no way we'll be caught,)] the reporter says as she senses your unease, [fia.speech(Besides, if we do get caught, you can deal with one guard, can't you? That's why I need a partner, after all; I couldn't put up much of a fight if I got caught, so I'm not going in there alone. It'd be no good you going in there solo either, as I need to be the one to see and report on what's down there. The only way the Enforcers would move against Sae would be if the public knew she was behind an illegal enslavement operation.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Seeing the logic in Fiammetta's assessment, you agree that the two of you should investigate this matter together.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(Great! So I'll meet you here between one and four then. Any day'll do; I'm near here every night visiting the bars to try and find leads on new stories. Sound good?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_ANGELIXX_DIARY_THROWN_OUT_END_CONTINUE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Seeing no other way to find out what's happened to the kidnapped refugees, you agree to Fiammetta's plan.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(Awesome!)] she happily cries, [fia.speech(Seeing as we're going to be partners in crime, you can call me 'Fia' from now on; that's what all my friends call me.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Telling Fia that you'll meet her again soon, you say goodbye to your new friend
		#IF(game.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_MAGIC_STORM)
			 and exit the bar, before wondering what to do now...
		#ELSE
			 and begin to [pc.walk] down the street, wondering what to do next...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Doll tour: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_DOLL_TOUR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although the autonomous sex dolls seem to be this store's main attraction, there's no price displayed for them anywhere, and so you ask Saellatrix how much they are.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(Oh, you're interested in buying one of our dolls?)] the succubus asks, [saellatrix.speech(Before I give you the price, I need to make sure that you know how truly exceptional they are. Follow me; I'll show you their features.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Stepping around from the other side of the counter, Saellatrix struts over towards the nearest corner of the shop. Realising that you're going to have to go through her sales pitch before being able to buy one of her dolls, you follow Saellatrix as she leads you to the doll display area. Her spaded tail slowly swishes behind her as she walks, and you can't help but gaze at her [saellatrix.assSize] ass as it rocks left and right in time with her steps.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(Here are our display models,)] the succubus declares as the two of you come to a halt before a square section of marble flooring that's been cordoned off with red rope barriers. Within this space are located three black silicone sex dolls, each one of which is completely identical to the others. The first doll is lying on her back with her legs spread, while the second is sitting on the first one's face. The third is performing a standing split beside the second, with her exposed groin hovering right next to the second's face.
	</p>
	<p>
		Although their pussies, assholes, and mouths have been left empty, you can quite clearly see that bright-pink dildos have been shoved deep into these dolls' fuckable nipples. Despite the fact that they're holding awkward poses and have their breasts stuffed full of sex toys, the dolls are all completely and utterly motionless.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(As you can see, our dolls are supremely flexible, and once in position they're able to remain completely motionless until ordered to move,)] Saellatrix says as she moves one of the red rope barriers aside and enters the display area. Stepping over to the doll who's performing a standing split, she gives her a hard push, causing her to topple over and fall to the floor. As she bounces down against the white marble, you see that the doll doesn't attempt to brace itself against the fall, and instead remains in its pose. After turning to make sure that you've seen this display, Saellatrix snaps down at the doll, [saellatrix.speech(Get back into position, cunt.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(They're totally and utterly obedient,)] Saellatrix says as she steps back over to you. As the doll quickly stands up and returns to her previous position, the succubus continues, [saellatrix.speech(They don't require food or drink either, so you can order them into a pose and then completely forget about them. Some of our customers even use these dolls as art installations, and leave them motionless for months at a time.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Reaching over to a button that's positioned on top of a nearby pedestal, Saellatrix presses it, causing the bright pink dildos which are inserted into the dolls' fuckable nipples to start vibrating. With that, all three of them reach down and start rhythmically rubbing their clits. Letting out lewd moans, they start to perform oral on one another, with the first greedily eating out the second and the second 
		#IF(game.isAnalContentEnabled())
			 hungrily rimming the third.
		#ELSE
			 doing the same to the third.
		#ENDIF
		 Smirking at you as the dolls pleasure one another, the succubus asks, [saellatrix.speech(Shall we continue? Or do you have any questions?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_DOLL_TOUR_OBEDIENCE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although you've just seen that one doll obey Saellatrix without question, you want to know if they're all obedient from the moment of purchase, or if they need training first.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(There's no need to train them,)] the succubus replies after you've asked your question. Going on, she explains, [saellatrix.speech(Dolls don't have free will; they'll do anything their owner commands. And by anything, I mean <i>anything</i>. Here, watch...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(Cunt, get over here!)] Saellatrix sharply commands the doll she just pushed over. Immediately doing as she's asked, the doll skips forwards to stand before the succubus, the pink dildos lodged deep in her tits continuing to vibrate as she awaits her next order. Instead of a command, however, she receives a sharp slap across her face. From the sadistic grin on her face, you see that Saellatrix is relishing this opportunity to abuse one of the dolls, and she happily lifts her hand to slap the unfortunate automaton again, and again, and again. Seemingly getting a little carried away, the succubus then grabs the doll by the throat, and after slamming it to the floor, she snaps, [saellatrix.speech(Lick my shoes, cunt, and thank me for the privilege!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Submissively crawling into position, the doll drops her head down and starts greedily licking Saellatrix's heels, saying in-between licks, [style.speechFeminineDoll(Thank you, mistress...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After letting the doll continue with this for a moment, Saellatrix kicks her away and orders her to return to the display. As the doll obediently hurries back to her previous position, the succubus turns to face you and asks, [saellatrix.speech(Was that a good enough demonstration? All dolls are incapable of refusing commands from their owners, or even understanding the concept of freedom. They don't have a personality, will never object to being fucked or abused, and are incapable of feeling embarrassed.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After you've told Saellatrix that her demonstration has made it clear that her dolls are completely obedient, the succubus asks, [saellatrix.speech(Shall we continue, or did you have another question?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_DOLL_TOUR_POWER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As she's claimed that dolls don't need to eat or drink, you want Saellatrix to explain how dolls get energy, and so ask her if you'd need to purchase batteries or feed them essences to keep them powered.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(As they're not living creatures, dolls don't have an aura of any kind, so trying to get them to absorb essences wouldn't get you very far,)] the succubus replies, before going on to explain, [saellatrix.speech(Our dolls are completely self-sufficient, and require no energy input from their owners whatsoever. The unique enchantment which my mother developed in order to animate these dolls also enables them to absorb background arcane energy, and that's what they use as a power source.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that being the case, you wonder what happens if a doll is exposed to high levels of arcane energy, and so ask Saellatrix if they have any issues with arcane storms.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(Not at all,)] the succubus replies, [saellatrix.speech(Being just an object which lacks an aura, our dolls don't get mentally affected by arcane storms, and the excess energy in the atmosphere does no harm to them whatsoever. In fact, our dolls gain a great deal of energy when exposed to arcane storms, so exposure to storms is actually good for them.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Gesturing towards the other side of the shop, Saellatrix asks, [saellatrix.speech(Shall we continue now?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_DOLL_TOUR_NEXT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Telling Saellatrix that you're ready to continue, you allow her to lead you over to the far side of the shop, where several dozen sex dolls have been lined up in regimented ranks. Much like the three you've just left behind, these dolls are all completely identical to one another, being made out of black silicone and taking the appearance of a human female in her early twenties. Thanks to the fact that they're not wearing a single item of clothing, and that they're completely bald, you're able to see that each one of them has a white barcode tattooed onto their forehead.
	</p>
	<p>
		Grabbing one of the nearest doll's DD-cup breasts, Saellatrix hefts and squeezes it in order to show off its realistic pliability as she explains, [saellatrix.speech(Our dolls are all made entirely out of arcane-infused silicone. That name's really just for convenience, however, as it's not actually silicone, but rather a similar material of my mother's creation. It feels as close to real flesh as you can get from an artificial substance, and thanks to its arcane nature, it remains within two degrees of a living person's body temperate.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Dropping her hands down to the doll's groin, Saellatrix pushes all eight of her fingers inside the artificial pussy, and she sadistically grins as she stretches it wide open. The doll remains completely motionless as the succubus then rams her entire fist and forearm into her cunt, growling as she does so, [saellatrix.speech(You like this, you dumb bitch?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.speechFeminineDoll(Yes, mistress,)] the doll obediently replies.
	</p>
	<p>
		Pulling her arm free and slapping the doll across the face, the sadistic succubus turns to face you and continues her sales pitch, [saellatrix.speech(As you can see, our dolls are extremely durable, and are able to withstand massive penetrations with no issue whatsoever. Thanks to the properties of their arcane-infused silicone, their orifices are also able to slowly absorb fluids, meaning that you never need to clean them out.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Wondering if there's any possibility of damaging the dolls by treating them in such a rough manner, you ask Saellatrix if it's a good idea to be abusing the dolls in such a manner.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(Oh, this is nothing for them,)] Saellatrix softly laughs in her posh accent, [saellatrix.speech(Our dolls have no internal components; they're just pure silicone with deep orifices, so there's no chance of breaking them. As they lack organs or anything of the sort, they're also immune to alcohol, addictive fluids, and psychedelics. Oh, and obviously they also can't get pregnant, so you can cum in them as much as you want without worrying about spawning some wretched bastard.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Giving the doll a quick slap across her tits, Saellatrix asks, [saellatrix.speech(So, shall we head back to the counter and discuss prices?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_DOLL_TOUR_NEXT_SILICONE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to know more about the material from which they're made, you ask Saellatrix if she can tell you more about this 'arcane-infused silicone'.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(As I'm sure you'll understand, the composition and manufacturing process is a trade secret,)] the succubus says, [saellatrix.speech(but if you wanted some technical details, then I can reveal that it's based on a certain siloxane polymer which exhibits elastomer properties, and then with our proprietary arcane-infusion method it's elevated far above any regular form of silicone.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Wanting to know more about the practical details of the material than its composition, you ask Saellatrix how the material affects the use of dolls. 
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(The main thing which owners should be aware of is that arcane-infused silicone is immune to all standard transformations,)] the succubus reveals. Grabbing the nearest doll and yanking her head down, she points to a three-hole port on the back of her neck, explaining as she does so, [saellatrix.speech(Dolls can still be transformed via this interface. We've got a special tool we call a 'DECK' - that's an acronym for 'Doll's Expedient Customisation Kit' - which plugs in here and can be used to modify the doll's appearance.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Releasing the doll's neck, Saellatrix smirks and reveals the catch, [saellatrix.speech(We do sell DECKs, but as they're extremely difficult and expensive to create, the cost proves to be prohibitive to all but the wealthiest of our clients. So, is there anything else you wanted to ask?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_DOLL_TOUR_NEXT_REALISM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you take a closer look at the dolls, you can't help but be impressed by the absurd level of detail they possess. Every single feature of a real body has been replicated in black silicone, right down to the cuticles of each nail, the correct number and shape of individual eyelashes, and even the pores on their faux skin. Wanting to find out how these dolls are made to look so realistic, you ask Saellatrix if she can tell you what her secret is.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(The secret is that Lovienne spent just as much time on the dolls' physical creation process as she did on their unique enchantment,)] Saellatrix says, [saellatrix.speech(In total, she worked on perfecting the creation of these sex dolls for almost two decades. That's the big secret.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With an elder lilin having devoted so much time to creating these sex dolls, you find yourself happy with that explanation of how they're so advanced.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(So, anything else, or shall we head on back to the counter to discuss prices?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_DOLL_TOUR_INTERRUPTION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having seen and heard enough, you tell Saellatrix to lead the way back to the counter. As she turns around, however, she finds that her passage is blocked by a short, fiery-looking young woman. With curly, black hair and tanned skin, she has a very Mediterranean appearance. Not wearing any makeup, and dressed in a black hoodie, daisy dukes, and a pair of sturdy-looking work boots, you get the impression that she doesn't care too much for fashion, and comes across as a bit of a tomboy. In her hands she's holding a notepad and pen, and looks to be ready to write down anything which anybody says.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fiammetta.speech(Hey, Sae! Can I get the statement you promised me now? Are the sex dolls you sell here made by transforming people?)] she asks Saellatrix in an energetic, accusatory manner.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(How <i>dare</i> you address me in such a manner!)] Saellatrix furiously replies.
	</p>
	<p>
		Laughing off the succubus's response, the stranger turns and locks her big, brown eyes onto you, before asking in an animated manner, [fiammetta.speech(Are you a new customer? I'm Fiammetta; a reporter with the Octogram Herald. Have you heard of the accusations against this establishment? Would you buy a doll if it was a transformed person?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_DOLL_TOUR_INTERRUPTION_NEXT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Surprised by the woman's words, you ask her what she means about people being turned into dolls. Before she can respond, however, Saellatrix shouts, [saellatrix.speech(Security!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		A pair of wolf-boy security guards immediately rush forwards and grab the reporter by the arms, before swiftly dragging her out of the front door and throwing her into the street.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(I do apologise about that,)] Saellatrix sighs, [saellatrix.speech(You've just witnessed the reason why I've got so many security guards working here. A group of conspiracy theorists somehow managed to convince themselves that these dolls are real people who we've transformed into dolls. The Octogram Herald got wind of it, and now they keep on sending journalists to harass me. If that wretched newspaper didn't have the protection of Lilith herself I'd have had it shut down long ago...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Feeling a little disconcerted by this turn of events, you look over at the realistic sex dolls, then ask Saellatrix why anyone would think that they're transformed people.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(It started with a couple of lunatics claiming that their wretched friends were kidnapped and sent here,)] she sighs, [saellatrix.speech(Then they started ranting and raving to random people in the street, claiming that we'd transformed their friends into sex dolls. Needless to say, we had to have the Enforcers arrest them, but the outrageous rumours they'd made up wouldn't go away. In the end we had to start offering public tours of our factory to show everyone how our dolls are made. Although that move managed to bring a halt to the rumours, the loathsome press haven't dropped the story yet...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Curious about these factory tours, you ask Saellatrix if she's still running them.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(Yes, you can have a tour of the factory later if you'd like,)] she replies, [saellatrix.speech(For now, however, let's head back to the counter and discuss doll prices. That's what we were doing before we were rudely interrupted, after all...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Without waiting for your reply, Saellatrix struts off towards the counter, leaving you to follow in her wake...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_DOLL_TOUR_FINISH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Following the succubus back to her starting place, you wait while she produces a very smart-looking sales brochure from under the counter and places it down before you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(Our standard model, which is the one you've seen on display, is the 'double-D',)] she explains in her posh British accent, [saellatrix.speech(With no optional extras, they start at a very reasonable two hundred thousand flames. Considering that you're effectively getting a slave without requiring a slaver license, these dolls really are a steal.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not quite sure if you'd describe a two hundred thousand flame sex doll as a 'steal', you ask Saellatrix what optional extras aren't included in the price.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(It's all in the brochure, if you'd care to take a look,)] she replies, pushing the black-and-gold booklet towards you. [saellatrix.speech(We can remove their barcodes, include a toy set, give them hair, or upgrade them to the double-H model. Oh, and we also offer special edition anthro models, but due to how much more difficult they are to make, they're somewhat more expensive. So, would you like to buy one now?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Although you're interested in taking a look at the brochure, you realise that you're going to need somewhere to store any dolls you buy. Not knowing what Lilaya's stance will be on sex dolls, you think that you'd better get her permission to store them before taking this any further...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Factory tour starting: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_FACTORY"><![CDATA[
	#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sex_shop_had_factory_tour))
		<p>
			Wanting to take Saellatrix up on her offer, you tell her that you'd like to have another tour of the doll factory.
		</p>
		<p>
			[saellatrix.speech(You do realise that I was just being polite when I said you could have another tour whenever you wanted, right?)] Saellatrix asks in a frustrated tone. Barely making an effort to hide her annoyance, she rolls her eyes before stepping over to the door behind the counter and opening it. Gesturing for you to follow her, she says, [saellatrix.speech(Come on then, let's get it over with.)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Wanting to take Saellatrix up on her offer, you tell her that you'd like to have a tour of the doll factory.
		</p>
		<p>
			[saellatrix.speech(Oh, you were serious when you asked if we're still running those tours?)] the succubus sighs. Barely making an effort to hide her annoyance, she rolls her eyes before stepping over to the door behind the counter and opening it. Gesturing for you to follow her, she says, [saellatrix.speech(Come on then, let's get it over with.)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		Impatiently tapping one of her feet, Saellatrix lets out another sigh as she waits for you to move...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FACTORY_TOUR_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.Walking] around to the other side of the counter, you follow Saellatrix as she steps through the door. On the other side, you find yourself
		#IF(saellatrix.getTotalTimesHadSex(pc)>0 || flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sex_shop_had_factory_tour))
			 once again
		#ENDIF
		 standing at the beginning of a corridor, which after a short distance takes a ninety-degree turn to the right. A door on the left is signposted as leading into the factory, and it's beside this door that Saellatrix comes to a halt.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(Ok, the tour starts now,)] the succubus says in her posh voice. Opening the door, she gestures for you to head on through, saying as she does so, [saellatrix.speech(You've got ten minutes in which to have a look around. If you have any questions then I'd rather you keep them to yourself, but if you must ask me something then please feel free to do so... Come on, I don't have all day.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not wanting to keep the succubus waiting, you quickly head on through the door and enter the doll factory. As Saellatrix closes and locks the door behind you, you take a moment in which to survey your surroundings.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FACTORY_TOUR_TIME_UP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(Your ten minutes are up,)] Saellatrix suddenly states in a stern, commanding tone. Strutting off in the direction of the exit, she calls out behind her, [saellatrix.speech(The tour is over, now please follow me.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With your curiosity momentarily satisfied, you follow the succubus as she leads you out of the factory...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FACTORY_TOUR_TIME_UP_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Allowing Saellatrix to lead the way, you follow in her footsteps as she leads you out of the factory. Clearly impatient to be getting back to the shop floor, the succubus moves with some haste, and you can't help but glance down at her sizeable rear end as her strutting gait causes it to hypnotically sway from side to side.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(If you see one of those wretched journalists, then you can tell them that there's nothing suspicious going on in here,)] Saellatrix says as she comes to a halt beside the door and turns to face you. Allowing her spaded tail to flick up and scratch an itch on one of her thick thighs, she sighs, [saellatrix.speech(Although the outrageous rumours about us transforming people into sex dolls have been quelled, those vultures from The Octogram Herald won't stop harassing me. Now that you've seen how we make the dolls, you'll be able to tell those hacks the truth if you see them.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Only after you've made a non-committal response does Saellatrix open the door, before leading you back to the counter and saying, [saellatrix.speech(If you'd like another tour of the factory then just let me know. Not today, though. Anyway, would you like to buy something? A doll, perhaps?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Saellatrix sex content: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_WAGER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the sound of Saellatrix's wager, you tell her that you'll take her up on it.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(Of course you will,)] the succubus confidently replies in her posh accent, [saellatrix.speech(Nobody would turn me down. Now follow me.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Turning her back on you, the succubus struts off to a door behind the counter, her [saellatrix.ass+] and [saellatrix.hips+] hypnotically swaying as she goes. Following her through this door, and then a short way down a corridor, you find yourself being led into the store's staff room. Unlike the basic sort of facilities found in most rooms of this type, the space before you has the appearance of a very upmarket bar. Black designer sofas have been placed around the edges of the room, while the fully-stocked bar itself is staffed by a couple of golden sex dolls. The soft light from a trio of expensive-looking chandeliers reflects off the polished marble floor, which causes Saellatrix's heels to make a loud clicking noise as she struts over to the bar.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(Get me a Vixen's Kiss,)] the succubus snaps at the nearest doll, [saellatrix.speech(and mix up a Face Fuck for [pc.name] here.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The two dolls quickly set about grabbing bottles from off the shelves behind the bar and pouring out exact measurements into two shot glasses. The first, the 'Vixen's Kiss', ends up as a fruity orange colour, with a bright red twist of glazed cherry perched on the rim. The drink which Saellatrix has ordered for you is quite clearly something more than an ordinary alcoholic drink, for it turns out to be an almost luminescent shade of yellow, with bright pink bubbles rising to create a grapefruit-coloured foam on the top.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(You like what I've done with this place?)] Saellatrix asks as you [pc.step] over to stand beside her at the bar. Telling her that it's more than you expected, you watch as the succubus downs her shot in one gulp. Opening her mouth, she allows her abnormally-long tongue to loll out, revealing to you that her throat is lined with a series of small, pulsating tentacles. Licking her [saellatrix.lips+], she reaches down to grope your [pc.cock+] as she seductively teases, [saellatrix.speech(I guarantee you've never had a blowjob quite like the one I'm about to give.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Strutting around to the other side of the bar, the succubus once again reveals that she has a sadistic streak as she slaps the nearest doll hard across the face. Still speaking in her posh British accent, she hisses, [saellatrix.speech(Move it, you dumb cunts.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As the two dolls hurry over to one corner of the room, their owner lies back over the bar top, allowing her head to hang down off the side right by where you're standing. Looking up at you, she teases, [saellatrix.speech(What are you waiting for? Drink up, then stick that delicious cock of yours down my throat. Remember, if you can snap my choker you get a lifetime discount. If not, then be prepared to pay double.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_WAGER_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sex_shop_discount))
			Although you've already snapped her choker and so earned a lifetime discount, you find yourself wanting to fuck Saellatrix's face once again. As such you tell her that you'll take her up on her wager.
		#ELSE
			Remembering how good it felt the last time, you find yourself wanting to fuck Saellatrix's face again. As such you tell her that you'll take her up on her wager.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(Well of course you want to fuck my throat again,)] the succubus confidently replies in her posh accent, [saellatrix.speech(Nothing else comes close to the experience I can provide.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Turning her back on you, the succubus struts off to a door behind the counter, her [saellatrix.ass+] and [saellatrix.hips+] hypnotically swaying as she goes. Following her through this door, and then a short way down a corridor, you find yourself once again being led into the store's staff room. Unlike the basic sort of facilities found in most rooms of this type, the space before you has the appearance of a very upmarket bar. Black designer sofas have been placed around the edges of the room, while the fully-stocked bar itself is staffed by a couple of golden sex dolls. The soft light from a trio of expensive-looking chandeliers reflects off the polished marble floor, which causes Saellatrix's heels to make a loud clicking noise as she struts over to the bar.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(Give me the usual,)] the succubus snaps at the nearest doll, [saellatrix.speech(and mix up another Face Fuck for [pc.name] here.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The two dolls quickly set about grabbing bottles from off the shelves behind the bar and pouring out exact measurements into two shot glasses. The first, which you recognise as a 'Vixen's Kiss', ends up as a fruity orange colour, with a bright red twist of glazed cherry perched on the rim. The drink which Saellatrix has ordered for you is quite clearly something more than an ordinary alcoholic drink, for it turns out to be an almost luminescent shade of yellow, with bright pink bubbles rising to create a grapefruit-coloured foam on the top.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(I always like a drink before swallowing cock,)] Saellatrix says as you [pc.step] over to stand beside her at the bar. Making a comment about the fact that she has a fully stocked bar at her disposal, you watch as the succubus downs her shot in one gulp. Opening her mouth, she allows her abnormally-long tongue to loll out, showing to you once again that her throat is lined with a series of small, pulsating tentacles. Licking her [saellatrix.lips+], she reaches down to grope your [pc.cock+] as she seductively teases, [saellatrix.speech(Ready to experience heaven again?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Strutting around to the other side of the bar, the succubus once again reveals that she has a sadistic streak as she slaps the nearest doll hard across the face. Still speaking in her posh British accent, she hisses, [saellatrix.speech(Move it, you dumb cunts.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As the two dolls hurry over to one corner of the room, their owner lies back over the bar top, allowing her head to hang down off the side right by where you're standing. Looking up at you, she teases, [saellatrix.speech(What are you waiting for? Drink up, then stick that delicious cock of yours down my throat. Remember, if you can snap my choker you keep your lifetime discount. If not, then be prepared to pay double.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_WAGER_DRINK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Picking up the shot glass, you down the bright yellow cocktail in one swift gulp. Immediately, you feel an unnatural wave of arousal surge through your body, giving you an intense desire to ram your cock into Saellatrix's open mouth. Looking up at you with a sly look on her face, the succubus teases, [saellatrix.speech(It's not called 'Face Fuck' for nothing. Now give me what I want...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_WAGER_NO_DRINK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding against drinking the bright yellow cocktail, you slide the shot glass down the bar top. Letting out a disappointed tut, Saellatrix looks up at you and teases, [saellatrix.speech(Oh well, your loss. Now give me what I want...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_WAGER_BLOWJOB_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isTaur())
			Doing as she says, you rear up and mount Saellatrix's face, before lining your [pc.cock+] up to her mouth.
		#ELSE
			Doing as she says, you pull out your [pc.cock+] and [pc.step] up to Saellatrix's face.
		#ENDIF
		 Letting out a hungry moan, the succubus darts out her abnormally long tongue, before wrapping it around your shaft and sliding it up and down. Finding yourself being jerked off by Saellatrix's warm, wet tongue, you're rock hard in seconds, and can't resist thrusting forwards to push your [pc.cockHead+] into her mouth.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speechNoEffects(~Mmm!~)] the succubus happily moans, continuing to use her tongue to stroke your cock as you push it down her throat. As your hard shaft slides down her slimy, warm passage, you feel the small tentacles which line her throat start to stroke and massage your throbbing length. Seemingly built for sex, the succubus's throat turns out to have extra muscles lining it, and as she starts gripping down and squeezing your shaft, you find yourself pushed to the limit of what you can endure. Unable to resist any longer, you buck your [pc.hips+] forwards and desperately slam your [pc.cock+] deep down Saellatrix's throat.
	</p>
	#IF(sex.isPenetrationDiameterTooBig(saellatrix.getFaceElasticity(), saellatrix.getFaceStretchedCapacity(), pc.getPenisDiameter(), true))
		<p>
			Her neck bulges massively as your thick shaft stretches her throat out and causes her to let out a gargled, horny splutter. Saellatrix's choker strains against the pressure for as long as it can, but the sheer girth of your fat cock is too much for it to bear. With a metallic 'ping', the chain holding it together at the back snaps, and with a great deal of satisfaction you watch the strip of black velvet fall to the floor. With your discount now earned, you can focus on how good it feels to receive a blowjob from this sexy succubus...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Although you see her neck bulging slightly as you begin to fuck her face, Saellatrix's choker shows no sign of snapping. Not wanting to dwell on the fact that you might not be big enough to earn that discount, you instead simply focus on how good it feels to receive a blowjob from this sexy succubus...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_WAGER_BLOWJOB_END"><![CDATA[
	#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sex_shop_choker_snapped))
		<p>
			With one last long, hungry lick up the entire length of your saliva-coated shaft, Saellatrix pushes you back and sits up on the bar top. After making a show of licking her [saellatrix.lips+], she turns to look at the dolls in the corner of the room. Snapping her fingers, she points to the floor where her broken choker has fallen and commands, [saellatrix.speech(Pick it up, cunt!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			While one of the dolls rushes forwards to hand the broken choker back to her mistress, Saellatrix playfully pouts at you and teases, [saellatrix.speech(I suppose you won the wager. I must say, it was worth it to get a taste of that fat, delicious cock of yours...)]
		</p>
		#IF(game.isNipplePenEnabled())
			<p>
				Snatching the choker from the doll who rushed to retrieve it for her, Saellatrix quickly bends its metal clasp back into position, before fitting it around her neck once more. Strutting around to your side of the bar, the succubus lets out a thoughtful hum and says, [saellatrix.speech(Now that I think about it, I really would rather not give you that discount. How about I offer you an alternative...)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Shrugging off her feminine blazer, the succubus unbuttons her shirt and tosses it to one side, leaving her wearing nothing above her waist but a black, lacy plunge bra. This quickly follows her shirt to the floor, leaving her huge, [saellatrix.cupSize]-cup breasts completely exposed. In contrast to the dark red skin which covers the rest of her body, both her massive, puffy nipples and the large areolae which surround them are ebony in colour. Around the rim of her left areola, the words 'Fuck Hole' have been tattooed in black ink, while 'Cock Sleeve' has been similarly written around the right one.
			</p>
			<p>
				[saellatrix.speech(Instead of giving you that discount, why don't I let you fuck my tits?)] she offers, pushing her fingers into her right nipple to demonstrate that they're penetrable orifices. Squatting down in front of you, she grabs your cock and pushes out her chest, rubbing your shaft over each of her nipples in turn. Looking up, she seductively teases, [saellatrix.speech(Go on, you know you'd rather have this. You can fuck my pussy and ass as well, if you'd like...)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Pressing her left nipple against your cock, she allows just the [pc.cockHead+] to push inside, and you can't help but let out [pc.a_moan+] as you feel the exotic orifice's internal tentacles trying to pull your shaft deeper inside. It looks like you'll have to decide which you'd prefer; getting a 25% discount in Lovienne's Luxuries, or getting to fuck Saellatrix any way you want...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Snatching the choker from the doll who rushed to retrieve it for her, Saellatrix quickly bends its metal clasp back into position, before fitting it around her neck once more. Strutting around to your side of the bar, the succubus smirks at you and offers, [saellatrix.speech(We should do this again some time. But not today.)]
			</p>
			<p>
				With that, the succubus strides off to the door through which you entered, leaving you to catch up with her...
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		<p>
			With one last long, hungry lick up the entire length of your saliva-coated shaft, Saellatrix pushes you back and sits up on the bar top. After making a show of licking her [saellatrix.lips+], she gives you a rather sinister smirk and gloats in her posh accent, [saellatrix.speech(Well, it looks like I won the wager. That's a real pity for you; I'll have to charge you double for everything from now on.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Strutting around to your side of the bar, the succubus lets out a thoughtful hum and says, [saellatrix.speech(Now that I think about it, making you pay double does seem a little harsh. How about I offer you a way out...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Lifting her miniskirt, Saellatrix drops her black, lacy panties to the floor and and kicks them off her feet. Looking down, you see that the succubus has fully exposed her ebony-lipped pussy. Her pubic hair has been shaved and trimmed down into the shape of a little heart, while above that she's got a black pentagram tattoo. Playfully biting her lip, she softly teases, [saellatrix.speech(You want to fuck my tight little pussy, hmm? Spread my legs and hilt your cock deep in my hot, wet cunt?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Before you can reply, the succubus lets out a mocking laugh, before evilly grinning at you and growling in a deep voice, [saellatrix.speech(I don't think so! If you want me to forget about doubling my prices, then <i>you're</i> the one who's going to get fucked, and fucked <i>hard</i>.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			As she says this,
			#IF(!saellatrix.isPregnant())
				 Saellatrix's pussy beings to visibly tighten, before closing up and disappearing entirely. In it's place,
			#ELSE
				 just above Saellatrix's pussy,
			#ENDIF
			 a thick bulge starts to grow out from her dark red skin, and as it increases in size it changes colour to ebony. Within moments, this bulge has transformed into a penis, and you can't help but watch as it rapidly grows in size to finally hang down at a staggering [saellatrix.penisLengthValues] in length.
			#IF(!saellatrix.isPregnant())
				 A massive pair of heavy, ebony balls then grow out from where her pussy used to be, before ponderously dropping down within their thick-skinned ball sack.
			#ENDIF
			 Transforming it into a cock that's worthy of a demon, Saellatrix grins as a fat, canine-like knot swells up at the base, before thick ribs and small, nub-like tentacles press out along its length.
			 Confidently stepping forwards, the succubus bucks her hips at you, causing her flaccid shaft
			#IF(!saellatrix.isPregnant())
				 and drooping balls
			#ENDIF
			 to swing forwards and back. Licking her lips, she lets out a wicked-sounding laugh and snaps, [saellatrix.speech(Get me hard, slut. You don't want to pay double for everything, do you?)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_WAGER_BLOWJOB_END_TAKE_DISCOUNT"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.isNipplePenEnabled())
		<p>
			Pulling your cock away from Saellatrix's tits, you tell the succubus that you'd rather take the discount.
		</p>
		<p>
			[saellatrix.speech(How disappointing,)] she tuts. Standing up, she once again snaps her fingers at her discarded clothing, ordering the nearby dolls as she does so, [saellatrix.speech(Dress me, you useless cunts.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Hurrying to obey, the golden dolls retrieve Saellatrix's bra, shirt, and blazer, before assisting the succubus in getting dressed. Instead of thanks, the dolls each receive a vicious slap across the face for their trouble, along with the reprimand, [saellatrix.speech(Be quicker next time. )]
		</p>
		<p>
			Turning back to face you, the succubus softens her tone and smirks as she says, [saellatrix.speech(We should do this again some time. But not today.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With that, Saellatrix strides off to the door through which you entered, leaving you to catch up with her. Following her through the door, you soon find yourself back in the main area of the shop, and after saying a quick goodbye, you [pc.step] away from Saellatrix's counter and wonder what to do next...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Following Saellatrix through the door, you soon find yourself back in the main area of the shop, and after saying a quick goodbye, you [pc.step] away from the succubus's counter and wonder what to do next...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_WAGER_NIPPLE_FUCK_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Too turned on to stop this and take the discount, you answer Saellatrix by pushing forwards and sinking your [pc.cock+] deep into her tight, fuckable nipple. The tentacles lining her insides instantly start stroking and massaging the entire length of your throbbing shaft, causing you to let out an involuntary [pc.moan].
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(~Mmm!~ That's right, I knew you wouldn't be able to resist,)] the succubus teases. Using one hand to hold up her breast so that it's easier for you to fuck, she drops the other down between her legs, and after hiking up her miniskirt and shifting aside her black, lacy panties, she starts to rub her clit. Clearly enjoying this just as much as you are, she lets out a horny moan and pants in her posh accent, [saellatrix.speech(Yes… ~Aah!~ Fuck me... Use my pussy #IF(game.isAnalContentEnabled())and ass#ENDIF if you want... ~Mmm!~ Yes! Fuck!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_WAGER_BLOWJOB_END_TAKE_PENALTY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not at all liking the sound of what Saellatrix is offering, you tell the succubus that you'd rather pay double than get fucked by the monster of a cock that's now hanging between her legs.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(How disappointing,)] she tuts. Instantly, her cock shrinks down and disappears back into the skin of her
		#IF(!saellatrix.isPregnant())
			 groin, before quickly being replaced by the pussy she had just moments ago.
		#ELSE
			 groin.
		#ENDIF
		 Picking up her panties, she slides them up her legs, before patting down her miniskirt and snapping, [saellatrix.speech(Follow me. We're done here.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the succubus strides off to the door through which you entered, leaving you to catch up with her. Following her through the door, you soon find yourself back in the main area of the shop, and after saying a quick goodbye, you [pc.step] away from Saellatrix's counter and wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_WAGER_FUCKED_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to pay double for everything in Saellatrix's store, you do as she asks and take hold of her massive, demonic cock, before starting to jerk her off to get her hard.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(Good choice, slut,)] the succubus sneers as her thick shaft stiffens and rises to attention. Letting out an excited, high-pitched moan, she suddenly slaps you across the face,
		#IF(pc.isCoverableAreaExposed(CA_MOUTH))
			 before pulling you into a deep, passionate kiss. Her long, strong tongue dominantly explores the insides of your mouth while you continue to stroke her cock.
		#ELSE
			 before leaning forwards and dragging her long, strong tongue over your neck and face.
		#ENDIF
		 Pulling back, she evilly grins at you and growls, [saellatrix.speech(You're mine now, slut. I'm going to <i>break</i> you...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not daring to stop now, you feel Saellatrix's thick, heavy cock throbbing in anticipation as you continue giving her a handjob...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_FUCKED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to pay double for everything any more, you tell Saellatrix that you'll submit to her in exchange for the penalty being removed.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(Of course you'll submit,)] the succubus arrogantly states in her posh accent, [saellatrix.speech(Everyone does what I want in the end. Now follow me, slut.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Turning her back on you, the succubus struts off to a door behind the counter, her [saellatrix.ass+] and [saellatrix.hips+] hypnotically swaying as she goes. Following her through this door, and then a short way down a corridor, you find yourself being led into the store's staff room. Unlike the basic sort of facilities found in most rooms of this type, the space before you has the appearance of a very upmarket bar. Black designer sofas have been placed around the edges of the room, while the fully-stocked bar itself is staffed by a couple of golden sex dolls. The soft light from a trio of expensive-looking chandeliers reflects off the polished marble floor, which causes Saellatrix's heels to make a loud clicking noise as she turns to face you.
	</p>
	<p>
		Lifting her miniskirt, Saellatrix drops her black, lacy panties to the floor and and kicks them off her feet. Looking down, you see that the succubus has fully exposed her ebony-lipped pussy. Her pubic hair has been shaved and trimmed down into the shape of a little heart, while above that she's got a black pentagram tattoo. Before you can say anything,
		#IF(!saellatrix.isPregnant())
			 Saellatrix's pussy beings to visibly tighten, before closing up and disappearing entirely. In it's place,
		#ELSE
			 just above Saellatrix's pussy,
		#ENDIF
		 a thick bulge starts to grow out from her dark red skin, and as it increases in size it changes colour to ebony. Within moments, this bulge has transformed into a penis, and you can't help but watch as it rapidly grows in size to finally hang down at a staggering [saellatrix.penisLengthValues] in length.
		#IF(!saellatrix.isPregnant())
			 A massive pair of heavy, ebony balls then grow out from where her pussy used to be, before ponderously dropping down within their thick-skinned ball sack.
		#ENDIF
		 Transforming it into a cock that's worthy of a demon, Saellatrix grins as a fat, canine-like knot swells up at the base, before thick ribs and small, nub-like tentacles press out along its length.
		 Confidently stepping forwards, the succubus bucks her hips at you, causing her flaccid shaft
		#IF(!saellatrix.isPregnant())
			 and drooping balls
		#ENDIF
		 to swing forwards and back. Licking her lips, she lets out a wicked-sounding laugh and snaps, [saellatrix.speech(Get me hard, slut. I can't wait to hear what lewd noises my fat cock's going to make you produce.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_FUCKED_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Doing as Saellatrix commands, you [pc.step] forwards and take hold of her massive, demonic cock, before starting to jerk her off to get her hard.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(That's it, slut, get a good feel of it,)] the succubus sneers as her thick shaft stiffens and rises to attention. Letting out an excited, high-pitched moan, she suddenly slaps you across the face,
		#IF(pc.isCoverableAreaExposed(CA_MOUTH))
			 before pulling you into a deep, passionate kiss. Her long, strong tongue dominantly explores the insides of your mouth while you continue to stroke her cock.
		#ELSE
			 before leaning forwards and dragging her long, strong tongue over your neck and face.
		#ENDIF
		 Pulling back, she evilly grins at you and growls, [saellatrix.speech(You're mine now, slut. I'm going to <i>break</i> you...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not daring to stop now, you feel Saellatrix's thick, heavy cock throbbing in anticipation as you continue giving her a handjob...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_WAGER_NIPPLE_FUCK_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With one last, lewd moan, Saellatrix moves back and pants, [saellatrix.speech(That's enough... Fuck...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As she brings an end to the sex, the succubus calls out to the dolls in the corner of the room, [saellatrix.speech(Come on, cunts, clean me up and help me get dressed.)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		Hurrying to do as their mistress commands, one of the golden dolls quickly gathers Saellatrix's clothing, while the other used several arcane wet wipes to clean her body. While you get your own things in order, the dolls help Saellatrix to get dressed, before hurrying back to their place behind the bar.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(That was an enjoyable break from the monotony of the day,)] the succubus declares, before commanding, [saellatrix.speech(Follow me. We're done here.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the succubus strides off to the door through which you entered, leaving you to catch up with her...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_WAGER_NIPPLE_FUCK_END_CONTINUE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Following Saellatrix through the door, you soon find yourself back in the main area of the shop, and after saying a quick goodbye, you [pc.step] away from the succubus's counter and wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_WAGER_FUCKED_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With one last, lewd moan, Saellatrix moves back and pants, [saellatrix.speech(That's enough, slut... Fuck...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As she brings an end to the sex, the succubus calls out to the dolls in the corner of the room, [saellatrix.speech(Come on, cunts, clean me up and help me get dressed.)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		Hurrying to do as their mistress commands, one of the golden dolls quickly gathers Saellatrix's clothing, while the other used several arcane wet wipes to clean her body. While you get your own things in order, the dolls help Saellatrix to get dressed, before hurrying back to their place behind the bar.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(That was an enjoyable break from the monotony of the day,)] the succubus declares, before commanding, [saellatrix.speech(Follow me. We're done here.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the succubus strides off to the door through which you entered, leaving you to catch up with her...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COUNTER_WAGER_FUCKED_END_CONTINUE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Following Saellatrix through the door, you soon find yourself back in the main area of the shop, and after saying a quick goodbye, you [pc.step] away from the succubus's counter and wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Factory scenes: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MEZZANINE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You're currently standing on a mezzanine floor which looks down onto the main area of the doll factory. The floor itself is made out of metal meshing, while yellow-painted guard rails run along the edge. Up above, large panels of arcane-powered lights hang down between metal ducts and pipes, illuminating the interior with a bright white glow.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.getCellFromLocation(1, 0).getPlace().getPlaceType()==PLACE_TYPE_GENERIC_IMPASSABLE)
			As you proceed along the mezzanine floor, Saellatrix gestures down at the factory floor and boasts, [saellatrix.speech(We've got all of the best equipment here. The average cost of each machine is easily more than five million flames.)]
		#ELSEIF(pc.getCellFromLocation(1, 0).getPlace().getPlaceType()==PLACE_TYPE_innoxia_dominion_sex_shop_toy_machines)
			Now at the far end of the mezzanine floor, Saellatrix points over to a large collection of machinery your right and states, [saellatrix.speech(We also manufacture toys here. The machines are right here, if you'd care to take a look.)]
		#ELSE
			Saellatrix steps up beside you and gestures down to the factory floor below, saying, [saellatrix.speech(This is where we manufacture our dolls. We can head on down and take a closer look if you'd like.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="TOY_MACHINES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.Stepping] into a recessed area at the end of the mezzanine floor, you find yourself standing before an impressive array of machines. Bright pink silicone dildos are travelling down a conveyor belt which links several of these machines to one another, and along the way an overhead nozzle sprays them with some kind of curing agent.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(We use the same technology for making these toys as we do for making the dolls,)] the succubus proudly states, before revealing, [saellatrix.speech(The entire process is automated. All that's required is for one of our technicians to perform a check every four hours.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasPerkAnywhereInTree(PERK_OBSERVANT))
			Although the conveyor belt's start and end is hidden by the impressive-looking machines, you quickly deduce from the size and shape of the assembly line that the dildos are simply going around in circles, almost as though the entire thing is simply for show...
		#ELSE
			Although the machinery looks very impressive, there's really not too much to see here. As such, you quickly decide to turn away and check out the rest of the factory...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="TOY_MACHINES_QUESTION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Convinced that these machines aren't actually doing anything, you ask Saellatrix why the dildos are simply going around in circles on the conveyor belt.
	</p>
	<p>
		Caught off-guard by your question, the succubus looks a little flustered for a moment, before quickly regaining her composure and brushing off your question by saying in a defensive tone, [saellatrix.speech(This is just the machine for setting the dildos into their final shape, so they're going around in circles as part of that process.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can ask a follow-up question, Saellatrix cuts you off by sternly asking, [saellatrix.speech(Are you a fabrication technician? No? I didn't think so, so don't try to pretend that you know how these things work. Come on, we don't have time for this.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Turning away from the machines, the succubus gesture for you to follow her and take a look at another part of the factory...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEPS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		This wide, metal staircase links the main area of the doll factory to the mezzanine floor up above.
		#IF(pc.getLastPlaceType()==PLACE_TYPE_innoxia_dominion_sex_shop_mezzanine)
			 As you travel downwards,
		#ELSE
			 As you travel upwards,
		#ENDIF
		 Saellatrix says in a flat, indifferent tone, [saellatrix.speech(Please mind your step.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="DOLL_MACHINE_A"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		A series of large, metal casts are arranged in a semi-circular fashion before you. Each one of them has been opened to reveal its contents, which consist of silicone limbs, torsos, and heads.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(Here's where we make the parts which are later assembled into dolls,)] Saellatrix explains, before stating, [saellatrix.speech(The arcane silicone takes an awfully long time to fully cure. Once they're set, they're taken on over to the next part of the assembly line by that slut right there.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Following Saellatrix's gesture, you look over to see a doll dutifully standing nearby. With nothing more to be seen in this area, you turn away from the motionless attendant and wonder where to go next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="DOLL_MACHINE_B"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Proceeding down the assembly line, you find yourself at the point where future dolls are being put together. The silicone limbs, heads, and torsos which were cast at the start of the line are being fitted together by two animated dolls, and you make a comment to Saellatrix about dolls making more of their own kind.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(Yes, it's rather prefect, isn't it?)] the succubus says in a smug tone, [saellatrix.speech(It's true that dolls don't work as quickly as a slave could, and they lack initiative, but for repetitive tasks like this they're perfect. They can also work non-stop, twenty-four hours a day, and don't need to be paid.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Strutting up behind one of the dolls, Saellatrix whips her spaded tail around and roughly thrusts it deep into the doll's exposed pussy. Reaching around to sadistically pinch the toy's thick nipples, she asks in a sharp tone, [saellatrix.speech(Are you working hard, you worthless cunt? You'd better be!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.speechFeminineDoll(Yes, mistress!)] the doll quickly replies. Continuing to work while Saellatrix roughly molests her, the doll adds, [style.speechFeminineDoll(I'm working as hard as I can!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Withdrawing her tail and taking her hands away from the doll's breasts, Saellatrix gives her victim a vicious slap on the ass before gesturing for you to continue on your way through the factory...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="DOLL_MACHINE_C"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Finding yourself at the end of the assembly line, you see that a dozen finished dolls are lined up in front of a large machine. Thick cables hang down from this machine at regular intervals, and are each plugged into a doll via a port on the back of their neck.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(This machine has been charged with the unique enchantment which my mother, the elder lilin Lovienne, created,)] Saellatrix proudly boasts, [saellatrix.speech(By the time it's finished, these inanimate toys will be fully autonomous sex dolls, just like that bitch there.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking over to one side of the machine, you see a sex doll standing at attention beside a control panel. It looks like she's monitoring and refining the enchantment process, for every few seconds or so she adjusts a dial or moves a lever.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(There's nowhere else in the realm which produces such high quality sex dolls,)] Saellatrix says in her posh British accent, [saellatrix.speech(The toys you see here will soon be making their new owners very happy indeed. Now, shall we move on?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="DOLL_MACHINE_STORAGE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Past the end of the assembly line, you find yourself in the area that's used for storing finished dolls. Several dozen of the black silicone toys have been lines up here in neat rows, waiting to be taken up to the shop once space is available for them.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(Impressive, don't you think?)] Saellatrix gloats, [saellatrix.speech(Our factory is able to finish a dozen dolls a day.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasPerkAnywhereInTree(PERK_OBSERVANT))
			Although at first glance these dolls look good enough, you notice that there are very faint, yet visible, gaps between their limbs and torsos. What's more, they're lacking the fine details of the dolls on display in the shop...
		#ELSE
			You've already seen enough dolls in the shop upstairs, and so there's not much here to interest you. Turning away, you prepare to head elsewhere in the factory...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="DOLL_MACHINE_STORAGE_QUESTION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Needing to know why there's a difference between these dolls and the ones in the shop, you ask Saellatrix why there are visible gaps between their limbs and torsos.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(What? Don't be silly, you're imagining things,)] the succubus snaps, before impatiently tapping her foot and saying, [saellatrix.speech(You're running out of time on your tour, so we need to move on to somewhere else. No more inspecting the dolls!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		It doesn't seem like you're going to get anywhere by pressing the point, so you turn away from the suspicious-looking dolls and wonder where to go next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Staff area dialogues: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CORRIDOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you return to the door through which you entered the factory, Saellatrix states, [saellatrix.speech(You still have some time left, but if you've seen enough then we can end this tour right now.)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		Waiting expectantly to hear your reply, the succubus taps her foot and lets out an impatient sigh.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="CORRIDOR_FACTORY_TOUR_CONTINUE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not yet wanting to end the tour of the factory, you tell Saellatrix that you'd like to continue.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(Then why did you return here?)] she pointedly asks. Not waiting for a reply, she turns and starts to walk back into the main area of the factory, calling back to you as she goes, [saellatrix.speech(Come on then, you don't have much time left.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="CORRIDOR_FACTORY_TOUR_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having seen enough, you tell Saellatrix that you'd like to end the tour. Clearly impatient to be getting back to the shop floor, the succubus quickly steps past you, and you can't help but glance down at her sizeable rear end as her strutting gait causes it to hypnotically sway from side to side.
	</p>
	<p>
		[saellatrix.speech(If you see one of those wretched journalists, then you can tell them that there's nothing suspicious going on in here,)] Saellatrix says as she comes to a halt beside the door and turns to face you. Allowing her spaded tail to flick up and scratch an itch on one of her thick thighs, she sighs, [saellatrix.speech(Although the outrageous rumours about us transforming people into sex dolls have been quelled, those vultures from The Octogram Herald won't stop harassing me. Now that you've seen how we make the dolls, you'll be able to tell those hacks the truth if you see them.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Only after you've made a non-committal response does Saellatrix open the door, before leading you back to the counter and saying, [saellatrix.speech(If you'd like another tour of the factory then just let me know. Not today, though. Anyway, would you like to buy something? A doll, perhaps?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Only accessible during the factory quest: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="STAFF_DOOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The door in front of you isn't locked, but as you turn the handle and peer into the corridor beyond, you suddenly freeze in your tracks. Although it's faint, you can hear the solitary security guard moving around somewhere within the shop floor. 
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(I told you he spends all night fucking that demo doll...)] Fia whispers from behind you. Sure enough, as you listen more closely, you realise that what you're hearing is faint grunts and wet smacking sounds.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(There's nothing this way but that fake factory and the shop floor,)] Fia quietly says, before tugging on your [pc.arm(true)] and saying, [fia.speech(Come on, let's go back the other way...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="STAFF_ROOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[fia.speech(Woah, look at this place,)] Fia mutters as the two of you enter the store's staff room.
		#IF(pc.getTotalTimesHadSex(saellatrix)>0)
			 Having already been shown this room by Saellatrix herself, your surroundings come as no surprise to you, but it's still impressive to see what the succubus has done with the place.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Unlike the basic sort of facilities found in most rooms of this type, the space before you has the appearance of a very upmarket bar. The beam from Fia's flashlight passes over several black designer sofas, before reflecting off a trio of expensive-looking chandeliers and then wandering over the polished marble floor to illuminate a fully-stocked bar on the far side of the room. Standing behind this bar are two golden sex dolls, but thankfully neither of them react to your sudden appearance, and remain completely and utterly motionless.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(That's kind of creepy,)] Fia mutters, [fia.speech(Come on, there's nothing for us in here, let's keep moving...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STAFF_DOOR_BACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to bump into the security guard, and with nothing to be gained from going through the door, you turn around and head back into the staff room...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BACK_DOOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thanks to the access card which Fia obtained from her friend, the two of you have been able to gain access to Lovienne's Luxuries. Standing beside the door via which you've entered the property, the two of you now have but one way to go in order to find the evidence you need to prove that Saellatrix and Angelixx are dealing in illegal slaves...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ELEVATOR_CORRIDOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		A pair of doors on either side of the staff room's bar lead into a short, undecorated corridor. In stark contrast to the luxurious room which its connected to, this corridor has a concrete floor, bare brick walls, and a maze of pipes running along the ceiling.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(That looks promising,)] Fia says as she points her flashlight towards an industrial elevator located at the far end of the corridor. Looking over at you, she guesses, [fia.speech(I bet that'll take us down to some offices, or even the real factory where Sae has her sex dolls made. I'm sure there'll be evidence of where those illegal slaves are down there...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ELEVATOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		A large, industrial elevator is positioned at the end of the corridor. As you and Fia approach, the doors slide open, bathing your surroundings in a cold, sterile light.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(Come on, [pc.name],)] your companion says, [fia.speech(We need to find out what's down there...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Stepping forwards, Fia eagerly motions for you to follow her...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

</dialogue>
