<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<!-- AUNT_HOME_PLAYERS_ROOM_QUICK_SHOWER -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="START_SHOWER_SEX_AS_DOM"><![CDATA[
	#IF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]==1)
		<p>
			Not wanting to finish your shower just yet, you slide your wet body up against [npc.name] and tell [npc.herHim] that now's the perfect time for you to fuck [npc.herHim].
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(npc.isAttractedTo(pc))
				Clearly feeling just as horny as you are, the [npc.race] lets out [npc.a_moan+] and leans in to plant a submissive kiss on your [pc.lips+]. With the shower's warm water cascading over your naked bodies, the two of you embrace one another and prepare to indulge in your lust...
			#ELSE
				Although [npc.sheIs] not attracted to you, the [npc.race] doesn't really have a choice in the matter, and lets out an anguished sigh as you lean in to plant a kiss on [npc.her] [npc.lips+]. With the shower's warm water cascading over your naked bodies, you embrace your slave and prepare to indulge in your lust...
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Not wanting to finish your shower just yet, you slide your wet body up against your slaves and tell them that now's the perfect time for you to fuck them.
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(npc.isAttractedTo(pc) && npc2.isAttractedTo(pc) && ([#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]==2 || npc3.isAttractedTo(pc)) && ([#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]<4 || npc4.isAttractedTo(pc)))
				Clearly feeling just as horny as you are, your slaves let out a chorus of excited moans, before all leaning in to plant a series of submissive kisses on your [pc.lips+] and [pc.breasts+]. With the shower's warm water cascading over your naked bodies, you all slide up against one another and prepare to indulge in your lust...
			#ELSEIF(!npc.isAttractedTo(pc) && !npc2.isAttractedTo(pc) && ([#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]==2 || !npc3.isAttractedTo(pc)) && ([#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]<4 || !npc4.isAttractedTo(pc)))
				Although none of your slaves are attracted to you, they don't really have a choice in the matter, and they let out a series of anguished sighs as you lean in to plant a kiss on each of their lips. With the shower's warm water cascading over your naked bodies, you embrace your reluctant slaves and prepare to indulge in your lust...
			#ELSE
				Although you can sense some hesitation, your slaves don't really have a choice in the matter, and you remind them of their place by leaning in to plant a dominant kiss on each of their lips. With the shower's warm water cascading over your naked bodies, you embrace your slaves and prepare to indulge in your lust...
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="START_SHOWER_SEX_AS_SUB"><![CDATA[
	#IF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]==1)
		<p>
			Not wanting to finish your shower just yet, you slide your wet body up against [npc.name] and tell [npc.herHim] that now's the perfect time for [npc.herHim] to do whatever [npc.she] wants with you.
		</p>
		<p>
			Clearly feeling just as horny as you are, the [npc.race] lets out [npc.a_moan+] and leans in to plant a dominant kiss on your [pc.lips+]. With the shower's warm water cascading over your naked bodies, the two of you embrace one another and prepare to indulge in your lust...
		</p>
	#ELSEIF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]==2)
		<p>
			Not wanting to finish your shower just yet, you slide your wet body up against [npc.name] and [npc2.name] and tell them that now's the perfect time for them to do whatever they want with you.
		</p>
		<p>
			Clearly feeling just as horny as you are, your slaves let out a pair of excited moans, before leaning in to plant a series of dominant kisses on your [pc.lips+] and [pc.breasts+]. With the shower's warm water cascading over your naked bodies, your two slaves slide up against you and prepare to take full advantage of your submission...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Not wanting to finish your shower just yet, you slide your wet body up against your slaves and tell them that now's the perfect time for them to do whatever they want with you.
		</p>
		<p>
			Clearly feeling just as horny as you are, your slaves let out a chorus of excited moans, before leaning in to plant a series of dominant kisses on your [pc.lips+] and [pc.breasts+]. With the shower's warm water cascading over your naked bodies, your slaves slide up against you and prepare to take full advantage of your submission...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AFTER_SHOWER_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SHOWER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(sex.getAllParticipants(false).size()==2)
			Having had your fun, you tell [npc.name] to quickly wash you off, and after [npc.sheHas] done so, you turn off the tap and get your slave to dry you off.
		#ELSE
			Having had your fun, you tell your slaves to quickly wash you off, and after they've done so, you turn off the tap and get your slaves to dry you off.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Satisfied with the fun that you were able to have while taking your shower, you get dressed and prepare to head back into your room...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AUNT_HOME_PLAYERS_ROOM_BATH -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="START_BATH_SEX_AS_DOM"><![CDATA[
	#IF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]==1)
		<p>
			Not wanting to finish your bath just yet, you slide your wet body up against [npc.name] and tell [npc.herHim] that now's the perfect time for you to fuck [npc.herHim].
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(npc.isAttractedTo(pc))
				Clearly feeling just as horny as you are, the [npc.race] lets out [npc.a_moan+] and leans in to plant a submissive kiss on your [pc.lips+]. With the bath's warm water enveloping your naked bodies, the two of you embrace one another and prepare to indulge in your lust...
			#ELSE
				Although [npc.sheIs] not attracted to you, the [npc.race] doesn't really have a choice in the matter, and lets out an anguished sigh as you lean in to plant a kiss on [npc.her] [npc.lips+]. With the bath's warm water enveloping your naked bodies, you embrace your slave and prepare to indulge in your lust...
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Not wanting to finish your bath just yet, you slide your wet body up against your slaves and tell them that now's the perfect time for you to fuck them.
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(npc.isAttractedTo(pc) && npc2.isAttractedTo(pc) && ([#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]==2 || npc3.isAttractedTo(pc)) && ([#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]<4 || npc4.isAttractedTo(pc)))
				Clearly feeling just as horny as you are, your slaves let out a chorus of excited moans, before all leaning in to plant a series of submissive kisses on your [pc.lips+] and [pc.breasts+]. With the bath's warm water enveloping your naked bodies, you all slide up against one another and prepare to indulge in your lust...
			#ELSEIF(!npc.isAttractedTo(pc) && !npc2.isAttractedTo(pc) && ([#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]==2 || !npc3.isAttractedTo(pc)) && ([#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]<4 || !npc4.isAttractedTo(pc)))
				Although none of your slaves are attracted to you, they don't really have a choice in the matter, and they let out a series of anguished sighs as you lean in to plant a kiss on each of their lips. With the bath's warm water enveloping your naked bodies, you embrace your reluctant slaves and prepare to indulge in your lust...
			#ELSE
				Although you can sense some hesitation, your slaves don't really have a choice in the matter, and you remind them of their place by leaning in to plant a dominant kiss on each of their lips. With the bath's warm water enveloping your naked bodies, you embrace your slaves and prepare to indulge in your lust...
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="START_BATH_SEX_AS_SUB"><![CDATA[
	#IF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]==1)
		<p>
			Not wanting to finish your shower just yet, you slide your wet body up against [npc.name] and tell [npc.herHim] that now's the perfect time for [npc.herHim] to do whatever [npc.she] wants with you.
		</p>
		<p>
			Clearly feeling just as horny as you are, the [npc.race] lets out [npc.a_moan+] and leans in to plant a dominant kiss on your [pc.lips+]. With the bath's warm water enveloping your naked bodies, the two of you embrace one another and prepare to indulge in your lust...
		</p>
	#ELSEIF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]==2)
		<p>
			Not wanting to finish your shower just yet, you slide your wet body up against [npc.name] and [npc2.name] and tell them that now's the perfect time for them to do whatever they want with you.
		</p>
		<p>
			Clearly feeling just as horny as you are, your slaves let out a pair of excited moans, before leaning in to plant a series of dominant kisses on your [pc.lips+] and [pc.breasts+]. With the bath's warm water enveloping your naked bodies, your two slaves slide up against you and prepare to take full advantage of your submission...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Not wanting to finish your shower just yet, you slide your wet body up against your slaves and tell them that now's the perfect time for them to do whatever they want with you.
		</p>
		<p>
			Clearly feeling just as horny as you are, your slaves let out a chorus of excited moans, before leaning in to plant a series of dominant kisses on your [pc.lips+] and [pc.breasts+]. With the bath's warm water enveloping your naked bodies, your slaves slide up against you and prepare to take full advantage of your submission...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AFTER_BATH_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_BATH_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(sex.getAllParticipants(false).size()==2)
			Having had your fun, you tell [npc.name] to quickly wash you off, and after [npc.sheHas] done so, you pull the plug and get your slave to dry you off.
		#ELSE
			Having had your fun, you tell your slaves to quickly wash you off, and after they've done so, you pull the plug and get your slaves to dry you off.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Satisfied with the fun that you were able to have while taking your bath, you get dressed and prepare to head back into your room...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Sex in player's room: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BED_SEX_START"><![CDATA[
	#IF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_0])
		<p>
			Before you can react, [npc.name] lowers [npc.herself] down over the top of you, pressing [npc.her] [npc.lips+] against yours and pulling you into a passionate kiss. Breaking it off a moment later, [npc.her] [npc.hands] start to roam down and grope your body as your horny slave [npc.moans], [npc.speech(Don't worry, [pc.name], I'll make this good for you as well...)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[#SPECIAL_PARSE_1] had obviously conspired to wait until you'd gone to sleep before pinning you down and having their way with you. Before you can react to the situation, [npc.name] lowers [npc.herself] down over the top of you, pressing [npc.her] [npc.lips+] against yours and pulling you into a passionate kiss. Leaning in on one side of you, [npc2.name] [npc2.moans], [npc2.speech(Don't worry, [pc.name], we'll make this good for you as well...)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BED_SEX_START_SLEEP"><![CDATA[
	#IF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_0])
		<p>
			Before you can react, [npc.name] lowers [npc.herself] down over the top of you, pressing [npc.her] [npc.lips+] against yours and pulling you into a passionate kiss. Breaking it off a moment later, [npc.her] [npc.hands] start to roam down and grope your body as your horny slave [npc.moans], [npc.speech(Don't worry, [pc.name], I'll make this good for you as well...)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[#SPECIAL_PARSE_1] had obviously conspired to wait until you'd gone to sleep before pinning you down and having their way with you. Before you can react to the situation, [npc.name] lowers [npc.herself] down over the top of you, pressing [npc.her] [npc.lips+] against yours and pulling you into a passionate kiss. Leaning in on one side of you, [npc2.name] [npc2.moans], [npc2.speech(Don't worry, [pc.name], we'll make this good for you as well...)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="POST_WAKE_UP_SEX"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.isAsleep())
		#IF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_0])
			<p>
				Having had [npc.her] fun with you, [npc.name] gently shuffles back and slips off your bed. Letting out a very satisfied sigh, [npc.she] teases, [npc.speech(I knew you wouldn't wake up...)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Completely unaware of what's happening, you snuggle down into your pillow and let out a soft sigh. Being such a deep sleeper, you aren't even close to waking up, and remain totally oblivious to [npc.namePos] presence as [npc.she] quietly slips away.
			</p>
			<p>
				...
			</p>
			<p>
				Some time later, you naturally wake up, and after letting out a yawn and sleepily opening your eyes, you realise that something's not quite right. Your body still feels tired, and with the evidence of fresh sexual fluids on your sheets, you realise that someone must have fucked you in your sleep.
			</p>
			<p>
				Getting out of bed, you wonder whether to do something about your night-time visitor, or to instead simply let [npc.herHim] be...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Having their fun with you, [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1] gently shuffle back and slip off your bed. Letting out a very satisfied sigh, [npc.name] teases, [npc.speech(I knew [pc.she] wouldn't wake up...)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Completely unaware of what's happening, you snuggle down into your pillow and let out a soft sigh. Being such a deep sleeper, you aren't even close to waking up, and remain totally oblivious to [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1] presence as they quietly slip away.
			</p>
			<p>
				...
			</p>
			<p>
				Some time later, you naturally wake up, and after letting out a yawn and sleepily opening your eyes, you realise that something's not quite right. Your body still feels tired, and with the evidence of fresh sexual fluids on your sheets, you realise that you've been fucked while sleeping.
			</p>
			<p>
				Getting out of bed, you wonder whether to do something about your night-time visitors, or to instead simply let them be...
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		#IF([#SPECIAL_PARSE_0])
			<p>
				Having had [npc.her] fun with you, [npc.name] allows you to collapse back onto your bed. Letting out a very satisfied sigh, [npc.she] [npc.moans], [npc.speech(See, that was fun for both of us, wasn't it?)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Interpreting your heavy breathing as a positive sign, [npc.name] smiles and asks, [npc.speech(Weren't you meant to be waking up at this time anyway?)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Realising that [npc.sheIs] right, you decide that you'd better get out of bed, and so, after a minute of lying back and catching your breath, you do just that. With a sigh and stretch of your [pc.arms], you allow [npc.name] to assist you as you gather your things, and with one final stretch, you get ready to set out once more...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Having had their fun with you, [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1] allow you to collapse back onto your bed. Letting out a very satisfied sigh, [npc.name] [npc.moans], [npc.speech(See, that was fun for all of us, wasn't it?)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Interpreting your heavy breathing as a positive sign, [npc2.name] smiles and asks, [npc2.speech(Weren't you meant to be waking up at this time anyway?)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Realising that [npc2.sheIs] right, you decide that you'd better get out of bed, and so, after a minute of lying back and catching your breath, you do just that. With a sigh and stretch of your [pc.arms], you allow [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1] to assist you as you gather your things, and with one final stretch, you get ready to set out once more...
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
